Usually in the Assassin's creed series the templars are the villains but then ubisoft created you play and people started calling them templars?
So ubisoft had no choice. They had to make the templars the good guys, and that's how rogue was created
So when you kill the templar in any of the Assassin's creed game day we usually tell you hahaha
You are actually the evil one, and you're a fool
different protagonists have had
Different reactions to this [hahaha]. No. I'm not going to say anything because that would make this assassination
Really awkward, so I'm thinking you're right, but I'm going [to] ignore you. Goodbye in this game
You play as chez [cormac] you first want to say fuck the assassins
So you're on this island?
Then you get the ship
Then you meet old man adewale the guy from black flag and you meet the killings the guy that was in the game that came
Before black line, so you're there playing with the other kids, but when you're done with that the game actually starts
[it] split up into two like the previous games
There's the sailing part which is pretty much exactly like black flag except with ice you?
Travel around, North America
And shoot at British tourists then you can board them and take everything they have then you remember that you're Irish in this game there
Will be no mercy at all no one will be spared the other part of the game is arrow shooting simulator
It's when you walk around and you shoot arrows at people. I guess there's also outside the animals
Inside the animus you know you're cool liars assassin, but outside you're guided walks around an office and fixes computers
it's
horrifyingly
Realistic so you get this mission to go out and kill some templars, but after you assassinate them it turns out
They're [not] really movie villains. They're more like hey. Che why did you assassinate me? That's that's not cool man
That's just rude. I mean what's what's up you get some stuff from them
You meet Benjamin Franklin the guy most famous for being first United States [ambassador] to sweden then she travels to lisbon
Probably lots of salt fish that's kind of what you do in lisbon. You eat salty fish
Then [then] he returns home, and he switches sides
I'm sure there was more to [it] than that
But as usual. I wasn't really paying attention
We templar now and you're out for revenge
ubisoft were afraid that you might still feel
Empathy for the Assassins so they created an assassin enemy unit. They hide in shit
And then scream when they attack you because of these guys I'm not sure I can ever play as an Assassin again
Fuck the assassins they released this game on the last gen consoles and Assassin's creed unity on the current gen and PC
But there was a problem as PC gamers complained about unity a small minority of us complained about it being
Completely unplayable most of us. Yes, didn't like the fact that for setting proms so they released rogue on PC
I have two major problems with this game one is that it never crashed?
I mean, it is a ubisoft game, and you have certain expectations
But they fail [to] deliver the [other] one is that it didn't
automatically scale down to 30 [FPS]
And I had FPS like over 60 and stuff and that made game
Not very cinematic [other] than those two problems. I kinda like it if you're interested in this game
You should probably check out another review, and that's the [kilian] experience
Subscribe like [Pana] check look at the other videos so yeah, I mean [solution]. There's that
you